DYLAN BUCKLEY

IT & CYBER SECURITY ENTHUSIAST

EXPERTISE expert adept amateur novice IT Administration (Managment, Migration etc.) Cyber Security (Red & Blue Team Scopes, Pentesting etc.) Programming (C, C#, Python, TS, GoLang etc.) Web Dev (Full Stack, Front-end + Back-end, Node, React etc.) Adobe CC Suite (Video Editing (Ae, Pr, En), Web (Xd, Dn))

CERTIFICATES

CP-400 HTML 4.0

National Computer Science Academy https://bit.ly/2XuqDD9

TOP 10% RANK FOR PHP

TestDome PHP Programming Certificate https://bit.ly/2ZS3Rm5

PROFILE

I'm a technology enthusiast with a passion for solving problems. It's with this passion where I've had a range of experiences in different types of technology. These experiences range from teaching people advanced video editing when I was younger, to even cyber security research. With my curiosity and attention to detail, I love applying my knowledge to help solve technical issues and to create unique solutions!

EDUCATION

PREP - YEAR 10 (Prep, Primary, Highschool) | JAN 2004 - APR 2015 Attended Prep to Year 10 at Cooloola Christian College in Gympie, QLD

QUEENSLAND CERTIFICATE OF EDUCATION (QCE) | APR 2015 - NOV 2017

Attended Year 11 & 12 as a Senoir Student at James Nash State High School

CERTIFICATE II - DIGITAL MEDIA & TECHNOLOGY | JAN 2017 - NOV 2017

While finishing high school and getting my Queensland Certificate of Education in Year 12, I completed a Certificate II in Digital Media & Technology. This certificate covered a range of topics including general programming, operating systems, networking, video editing and basic computer hardware knowledge.

BACHELOR OF INFORMATION TECHNOLOGY | JAN 2018 - PRESENT

I am currently a student studying at the Queensland University of Technology (majoring in computer science). It has been an amazing experience with a great community of technologists who I see through club meetings (some clubs include CodeNetwork & the QUT White Hat Society).

SELECTED EXPERIENCES

VIDEO EDITING | SEP 2012 - OCT 2016

Before I found my passion for IT & Security, I was heavily involved in video editing. Starting from 2012 (at the age of 12) I made guides on YouTube teaching people how to utilise After Effects CC for VFX (Visual Effects). I have since moved on to bigger and better technologies, but as of 2021 the channel currently has over 18,000 subscribers with a total of 1.2 million views.

MAYFLY - LOW BUDGET SHORT FILM | AUG 2013 - SEP 2013

At the age of 13, because I was noticed from YouTube, a short film director approached me from the US and hired me to work on the VFX for a Kickstarter project. It was the first paid job for my visual effects skills. I learnt a lot about time management, communication & how to organise workflows for a client.

FREELANCING WEB DEVELOPMENT | JAN 2016 - DEC 2017

During my last years in highschool, I decided to work online and freelance my technology skills to gain experience. Some freelancing jobs included web technologies such as web design, full stack development, datasebase management, server migration, api's and even serverless migration.

SELECTED PROJECTS

PASCRA | LATEST RELEASE DATE: NOV 10th, 2020

Pascra (Pastebin Crawler) is a Go tool created to crawl & download ANY "pastes" created by users on pastebin.com. It ustilises the colly library along with an OS command call to wget to be able to download, allowing for cross-platform use. It written in under 48 hours to get a feel for GoLang.

SURGE | LATEST RELEASE DATE: May 13th , 2020

SURGE is an assessment item I completed at the Queensland University of Technology. The goal assigned was to create a front-end React app with a back-end server serving NYSE data to the app. Completed in 5 days I got a GPA 7 (A+) & It was my first experience learning in React as well as the new web development paradigm.

PHE-API | LATEST RELEASE DATE: Unknown, 2015

The PHE-API (PHP HOST ENUMERATION API), pronounced fe · api, was my first taste for a software engineering project. It used PHP to fetch a hostname (URL, or IPv4), and return the response data to the webpage. After redesigning the tool, the final version used AJAX requests to return response data formatted as JSON to the console.

CONTACT

email: me@dylanbuckley.net alt: dylan.buckley9@gmail.com phone: 0498 949 217 github: z89